cow-keeper-coin.com 2016-10-23

# Cow keeper coin

s:4267:"

The privacy of all customers to [http://cow-keeper-coin.com](http://cow-keeper-coin.com/)[](http://www.freebitcoins4u.co.uk/) is very important to us.

At [http://cow-keeper-coin.com](http://cow-keeper-coin.com/), we understand the importance of keeping your personal information private.   

Below you will find the types of personal information we collect when you access and visit [http://cow-keeper-coin.com](http://cow-keeper-coin.com/) and how we always try to safeguard your information.   

We do not sell personal information to third parties.

Log Files As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.   

The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

We also use third party advertisements on [http://cow-keeper-coin.com](http://cow-keeper-coin.com/) to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing EU clothing store ads to someone in the EU, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing investing ads to someone who frequents investment sites).

Cookies and Web Beacons We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.   

This could include only showing you an advertisment once on your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as posting comments.

DoubleClick DART cookies We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Googles DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting New York, you may see New York hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about Tennis). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallows cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

";
